Are ya ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Aye-aye, Captain!
是的，队长！
I can't hear you!
我听不到你说话！
Aye-aye, Captain!
是的，队长！
♪ Oh ♪
♪哦♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
♪ 吸水性、黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
♪ 如果是航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
♪ 然后掉到甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
- ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
- Ready?
- ♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
- 准备好了吗？
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
Argh!
啊！
Huh?
啊？
Ugh, I am so hungry
呃，我好饿
and incapable of doing
anything for myself!
并且无能为力
为了自己什么都可以！
You're in luck,
my slovenly friend!
你很幸运，
我的邋遢朋友！
While you sit there
wallowing in your filth,
当你坐在那里时
沉溺于你的污秽之中，
you can let the Krusty Krab make
and deliver your meal for ya!
你可以让蟹堡王做
并为您送餐！
If your food isn't in your hands
in ten minutes or less,
如果你的食物不在你手中
在十分钟或更短的时间内，
it's f-f-f...
这是 f-f-f...
Pssst!
嘘！
The line is,
"Free."
这条线是，
“免费。”
Yeah, what he said.
是的，他说的。
Thank you, Krusty Krab!
谢谢你，蟹堡王！
You're welcome!
不客气！
Where's me money?
我哪里有钱？
Little did they know
their Krusty commercial
他们知之甚少
他们的 Krusty 广告
would reach
the ignoble eyes of...
将达到
卑鄙的眼睛……
the League of E.V.I.L.!
邪恶联盟！
Mmm! I love those greasy
Krabby Patties!
嗯！我喜欢那些油腻的
蟹肉饼！
Yeah, but I hate
paying for things!
是的，但我讨厌
付钱买东西！
Well, if I don't get
好吧，如果我没有得到
my afternoon snackies,
我的下午点心，
I'm gonna throw a tantrum!
我要发脾气了！
You're right! This calls for
a deliciously diabolical scheme.
你说得对！这需要
一个极其邪恶的计划
Whoop!
哎哟！
We place our order
with the Krusty Krab,
我们下订单
和蟹堡王一起，
then use our powers of evil
然后使用我们的邪恶力量
to ensure the delivery boy
is late!
确保送货员
迟到了！
Then we get a free lunch!
然后我们就可以得到免费的午餐了！
Laugh with me, villains! Laugh!
和我一起笑吧，恶棍们！笑！
Shh, shh!
嘘，嘘！
- Krusty Krab!
- Hello?
-蟹堡王！
- 你好？
I'd like five Krabby Combos,
extra Krusty sauce...
我想要五个蟹蟹组合，
额外的Krusty酱...
Hey!
嘿！
Oh. Make that four and
a Pipsqueak Patty kid's meal.
哦。使这四个和
Pipsqueak Patty 儿童餐。
Make it out to...
Man Ray!
让它出来...
曼·雷！
Deliver to League of E.V.I.L.
secret hideout,
交付给 E.V.I.L. 联盟
秘密藏身处，
Ominous Alley, behind
the gas station. Thank you!
不祥的小巷，后面
加油站。谢谢你！
- No, thank--
- Villains!
- 不用了，谢谢--
- 恶棍！
Battle stations!
战斗站！
Meanwhile!
同时！
Now remember, SpongeBob,
this delivery's gotta be quick,
现在记住，海绵宝宝，
这次送货一定要快
and you gotta put it directly
in the customer's hand.
你必须直接把它
在客户手中。
I ain't givin' out
no free meals!
我不会放弃
没有免费餐！
Aye-aye, sir!
是啊，先生！
Uh, but...
呃，但是...
Think I'll have time
for the villains
我想我会有时间
对于恶棍来说
to sign my comic book?
签署我的漫画书？
Just get in the cannon.
只要进入大炮即可。
Whoosh!
嗖嗖！
Pull!
拉！
Slam!
猛击！
Huh?
啊？
"Secret entrance."
Sounds villainous!
“秘密入口。”
听起来很邪恶！
This must be the place!
一定是这个地方！
Huh?
啊？
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
- Oh. Wait a second.
- Thinking quickly,
- 哦。等一下。
- 快速思考，
SpongeBob reached for
his hydrodynamic spatula
海绵宝宝伸手去拿
他的流体动力铲
with port and starboard
attachments!
左舷和右舷
附件！
Eight minutes to spare!
还剩八分钟！
This'll be a walk in the park.
这将是在公园散步。
Eh... I mean, cave.
呃...我的意思是，洞穴。
Whattaya want, bub?
小伙子想要什么？
Krusty delivery!
库斯提送货！
Hey, I know you!
嘿，我认识你！
- You're...
- Helen the Felon!
- 你是...
- 重罪犯海伦！
The trouble-making tyke!
这个惹麻烦的家伙！
That's right.
这是正确的。
And I'm giving you a time-out!
我给你一个暂停时间！
B-But I'm making a delivery!
但、但我正在送货！
And Mr. Krabs says I have to
put it right in your hand!
蟹老板说我必须这么做
把它放在你的手里！
Not my hand.
不是我的手。
Man Ray's hand!
曼雷之手！
You're gonna have to open this
door if you wanna get to him.
你必须打开这个
门，如果你想接近他。
Okay!
好的！
Huh?
啊？
Yah!
啊！
Whoa!
哇！
Give up the bag,
buddy boy!
放弃包包，
伙计男孩！
You'll never make it
to Man Ray on time!
你永远不会成功
准时到曼雷！
Never!
绝不！
Too weak to turn knob...
太弱了，无法转动旋钮...
I'll use
my patty flipping hand!
我会用
我的小馅饼翻转手！
Huh? No fair! That's cheatin'!
啊？不公平！那是作弊！
Whoa!
哇！
Concussed!
脑震荡！
Sorry about that.
对此感到抱歉。
Say, can I get your autograph?
说吧，我可以要你的签名吗？
Of course!
当然！
Gee, thanks!
哎呀，谢谢！
Six minutes to spare.
还剩六分钟。
Krusty delivery!
库斯提送货！
Huh?
啊？
I can't believe it! That's...
我简直不敢相信！那是...
Jumbo Shrimp!
大虾！
The biggest name
in bad behavior!
最响亮的名字
行为不端！
And just where do you think
you're going, small fry?
你认为哪里
小鲜肉，你要去吗？
K-Krusty delivery...
for Man Ray?
K-Krusty交付...
为了曼·雷？
If you wanna get to him,
you'll have to go through me!
如果你想接近他，
你必须通过我！
No! Please!
不！请！
Huh?
啊？
Puny!
微不足道！
You look bigger in the comics.
你在漫画里看起来更大。
Do you think you could
sign this for me?
你认为你可以吗
帮我签这个吗？
Oh, gladly.
哦，很高兴。
So, uh, you're a fan?
那么，呃，你是粉丝吗？
Oh... Huge!
哦……巨大！
Wait!
等待！
I'm not done with you,
little guy!
我和你还没完
小家伙！
Get back here!
回到这里！
Four minutes!
Better hurry!
四分钟！
最好快点！
Where am I?
我在哪里？
I... must have taken
a wrong turn.
我……一定是拿走了
转错了方向。
You certainly did,
you simpleminded sponge!
你当然做到了，
你这个头脑简单的海绵！
Prepare to be ensnared by the--
准备好被——
The Dirty Bubble! Ooh!
Can I get your autograph?
肮脏的泡泡！哦！
我可以得到你的签名吗？
No! N-no, wait!
不！不、不，等等！
- Not again!
- Pop!
- 不再有！
- 流行！
Dirty Bubble.
肮脏的泡泡。
Hmm. Now where's Man Ray?
唔。现在曼·雷在哪里？
Um...
嗯...
K-Krusty d-delivery!
K-Krusty d-送货！
Hmm?
唔？
I should have known!
我早该知道的！
It's, uh... It's, uh...
这是，呃……这是，呃……
Eh?
呃？
Sub-Marinara!
潜艇！
The maniacal meatball sub!
疯狂的肉丸子！
No matter.
不管。
I could never be defeated
by food.
我永远不会被打败
通过食物。
I am a... fry cook!
我是一名...炒菜厨师！
Saucy!
俏皮！
Oh!
哦！
Breaded!
面包屑！
Oh, no!
哦，不！
I've been defeated by food!
我被食物打败了！
Oh, no! This sinister
spuccadella is preparing
哦，不！这险恶的
斯普卡德拉正在准备
to marinate our hero
in his famous extra spicy
腌制我们的英雄
以他著名的特辣
molten arrabbiata sauce!
融化的arrabbiata酱！
How will SpongeBob escape
this harrowing hoagie?
海绵宝宝将如何逃脱
这个令人痛苦的三明治？
Oh, don't worry, Mr. Narrator,
I know what to do!
哦，别担心，旁白先生，
我知道该怎么做了！
Well, then do it!
好吧，那就开始吧！
Looks like I filled up on bread!
看来我吃面包已经饱了！
Now to wrap up the leftovers.
现在把剩菜包起来。
Will you sign this for me?
你愿意帮我签这个吗？
Uh... thanks.
呃...谢谢。
Looks like you've been
foiled again!
看来你已经
再次挫败！
Extra fresh!
特别新鲜！
While I wait
for my delivery,
当我等待时
为了我的交货，
I might as well kill some time!
我还不如消磨点时间呢！
The Tremendous Trunk!
巨大的树干！
The elephant seal
whose nose knows all!
象海豹
谁的鼻子知道一切！
Let me go, Man Ray!
放开我，曼雷！
I've already sniffed out
your evil deeds!
我已经嗅出
你的恶行！
The only thing
you'll be sniffing...
唯一的一件事
你会吸...
is this stinky cheese!
这是臭奶酪吗！
No! Not Limburger!
不！不是林堡！
I have children!
我有孩子了！
Krusty delivery!
库斯提送货！
And with ten seconds to spare.
还有十秒钟的时间。
Ooh, my lunch order.
哦，我的午餐订单。
Well, go ahead
and put it in my hand.
好吧，继续吧
并把它放在我手里。
Oops!
哎呀！
Yes! Delivery complete!
是的！发货完成！
Yes, but it was...
是的，但那是...
one second late!
晚了一秒！
Overdue!
逾期了！
That means...
这意味着...
...our meal...
...我们的饭菜...
...is free!
...是免费的！
Laugh at him, villains!
嘲笑他吧，恶棍们！
Laugh!
笑！
Hey, kid!
嘿，孩子！
A little help here?
这里有一点帮助吗？
Oh, hi, Tremendous Trunk.
哦，嗨，巨大的树干。
Sure, I'll free you.
当然，我会释放你。
Ha-ha!
哈哈！
Can I have
your autograph?
我可以有
你的签名？
Here you go!
干得好！
But listen, pal, you helped me,
so I'll help you!
但是听着，朋友，你帮助了我，
所以我会帮助你！
With the prodigious power
拥有惊人的力量
of his potent proboscis...
他强大的长鼻......
...The Tremendous Trunk
sneezed SpongeBob
...巨大的树干
海绵宝宝打喷嚏
back through time itself!
回到过去！
One minute
and seven seconds earlier!
一分钟
七秒前！
Huh? Oof!
啊？钱币！
Krusty delivery... delivered!
Krusty 交付...交付！
Aw...
噢...
- That'll be $12.
- Uh, well, you see...
- 那是 12 美元。
- 呃，好吧，你看...
The League of E.V.I.L.
is actually broke.
E.V.I.L.联盟
实际上已经破产了。
Turns out crime doesn't pay.
事实证明，犯罪是没有代价的。
Oh. Well, that's okay.
哦。好吧，没关系。
I'll cover it!
我来遮盖它！
Ooh! Thanks for the tip!
哦！谢谢你的提示！
Sign here, please.
请在这里签名。
Thank you, evil villains!
谢谢你们，邪恶的恶棍！
No! Thank you, SpongeBob!
不！谢谢你，海绵宝宝！
Ah-choo!
啊呼！
Gesundheit!
完全安全！
Thanks.
谢谢。
End!
结束！